http://www.aerofilmsystems.com/privacy-statement

Privacy policy
How do we deal with your personal data?Aerofilm Systems attach great importance to the protection of your personal data. In the course of our business, it is sometimes necessary for us to ask you for personal data and to process this data. When we do this, we always act with the utmost care and in accordance with the law. In this Privacy statement, we indicate what personal data of yours we process when you visit one of our websites and provide your personal data, how we do this and what rights you have in that respect.
1. Why do we process your personal data?
If you use one of our products or services, we can collect and process your personal data. For instance, this could be the personal data you provide when you fill in a contact or interest form, request a brochure, or it could be the data that we collect when you use one of our websites.We use your personal data for, among other things, the following purposes:To comply with an agreement;To process your request for information or brochures;To deal with your complaint;To process your job application;To offer products and services.When using the term personal data, we are referring to any information regarding an identified or identifiable natural person.We process personal data in accordance with the prevailing legal obligations and solely for the purposes for which we have obtained these personal data.
2. Legal basis for the use of your personal data
We only process your personal data if you have given permission for same when you provided your personal data, if we have a legitimate interest in same or if we are required to meet a legal obligation. You may withdraw your permission at any time. We will then no longer process your personal data, unless there are legal grounds for same.
3. Sharing personal data
We only share your personal data with third parties if:You have given your permission for same;We are obliged to do so in pursuance of the law, a judicial order or the order of an authorized regulatory body;We or a third party have a legitimate interest that justifies the sharing of your personal data.For instance, we may share your personal data with third parties if this is necessary to execute an agreement between you and Aerofilm Systems. If we provide third parties with access to your personal data, we do so solely if we are certain that this third party will use your personal data solely in a manner for a purpose that is related to the purpose for which we obtained your personal data, and only in accordance with legal requirements. We close a processing agreement with third parties that process your personal data at our behest, such to ensure that the security of the personal data to be processed meets all legal requirements. Aerofilm Systems remains responsible for this processing.In some cases, we are obliged by law to pass on personal data to third parties, such as the police. We may also be subject to a legal obligation to pass on personal data if this is necessary in the interest of state security, the prevention or detection of criminal acts or if the interests of other people are at stake. In all other cases, we may only provide third parties with your personal data if you have given express permission for same. We store our personal data on servers in the European Economic Area (EEA), unless explicitly stated otherwise.
4. Cookies and hyperlinks
We make use of functional, analytical and tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is saved in the browser of your computer, tablet or smartphone on your first visit to our website. We use cookies with a purely technical functionality. These ensure that our website functions properly and for instance that it remembers your preferences. We also use these cookies to ensure that our website functions effectively to enable us to optimize our website. In addition to this, we place cookies that log your surfing behavior, so we can offer you tailor-made content and advertisements. We inform you about these cookies at your first visit to one of our websites.You can decline cookies by setting up your browser in such a way that it no longer saves cookies. In addition, you can remove all previously saved cookies via the settings in your browser.
5. Your right to object
You can object to the use of your personal data, for instance if you believe that use of your personal data is not necessary for the execution of our activities or to meet a legal obligation. You may object by sending a letter clearly stating what you are objecting to, complete with your name, address, telephone number and a copy of a valid proof of identity to info@aerofilmsystems.com, addressed for the attention of the Privacy Officer. Please do not forget to obscure your BSN on the copy of your ID document before you send this. We will make sure you receive a reply within four weeks. In the case of complex requests, this term may be extended by a second term of four weeks.
6. Your other rights in connection with the processing of your personal data
In addition to your right to object, you have a number of other rights with respect to your personal data:You have the right of access to your personal data. This means you have a right to submit a request for information on what personal data of yours has been registered and the purposes for which this is being used.If you believe we have incorrect personal data about you, you can have this personal data corrected. You also have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your personal data, including during the period of time we need to assess your requests or objections.You can ask us to erase your personal data from our systems. We will comply with your request, unless we have an urgent, legitimate interest in not erasing the personal data that outweighs your right to privacy. If we have erased your personal data, we cannot for technical reasons immediately erase every single copy of your personal data from our systems and back-up systems. Finally, you have the right to ask us to cooperate in the transfer of your personal data to another party. We will only refuse your request if a request is submitted with unreasonable frequency, requires an unreasonably major technical effort or has an unreasonably major technical impact on our systems, endangers the privacy of others or is extremely impractical. You can submit a request in the manner described in point 6. We would also like to alert you to the possibility of submitting a complaint to the Dutch Data Protection Authority.
7. Term of retention
We retain personal data no longer than is strictly necessary for the purposes for which the personal data was collected, unless there are legal grounds to retain your data for longer.
8. How do we secure your personal data
We make use of functional, analytical and tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is saved in the browser of your computer, tablet or smartphone on your first visit to our website. We use cookies with a purely technical functionality. These ensure that our website functions properly and for instance that it remembers your preferences. We also use these cookies to ensure that our website functions effectively to enable us to optimize our website. In addition to this, we place cookies that log your surfing behavior, so we can offer you tailor-made content and advertisements. We inform you about these cookies at your first visit to one of our websites.You can decline cookies by setting up your browser in such a way that it no longer saves cookies. In addition, you can remove all previously saved cookies via the settings in your browser.
9. Information on the party responsible for the processing of your personal data
The party responsible for the processing of your personal data is Aerofilm Systems BV, Adriaan Mulderweg 16. 5657 EM Eindhoven. Chamber of Commerce (KvK) no. 17053698.
10. Changes to the privacy statement
Aerofilm Systems reserves the right to unilaterally change the provisions of this privacy statement. We will publish any changes on our website, where you will always find the most up-to-date version. We advise you to visit the website on a regular basis.
Aerofilm Systems ontwerpt, ontwikkelt en produceert luchtkussens en luchtkussen transportsystemen. Deze vorm van intern transport is de ideale oplossing om lichte tot zeer zware objecten op een veilige, ergonomische en kostenbesparende manier te verplaatsen en positioneren. Ook voor gevoelige en daarom vaak dure objecten is het ideaal, omdat luchtkussens geen trillingen veroorzaken tijdens verplaatsing.
Headoffice
Aerofilm Systems B.V.
info@aerofilmsystems.com
Tel: +31 40 255 03 03
Adriaan Mulderweg 16
5657 EM Eindhoven
The Netherlands
USA
Aerofilm Systems Inc.
info@aerofilmsystemsinc.com
Tel: +1 317 804 9481
17408 Tiller Court
Westfield, Indiana
United States
Germany
Aerofilm Systems GmbH
info@luftkissensysteme.com
Tel: +49 2821 7194 979
Siemensstraße 31
D-47533 Kleve
Germany
© 2020 Aerofilm Systems B.V. | All rights reserved | Powered By E-Expansion | Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions
This website uses cookies to make sure you'll have the best possible experience. If you keep using this website, you'll automatically agree to the privacy statement. AcceptPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Sluiten
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Noodzakelijk
Altijd ingeschakeld
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Niet-noodzakelijk
Niet-noodzakelijk
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Bel ons/ Call us
+31 40 2550303
Call us
+1 317 804 9481
Rufen Sie uns an
+49 28217194979
Discover air casters: the ideal solution for moving light to very heavy objects
Learn how air casters can help you to move light, heavy or sensitive objects in a safe, ergonomic, and cost-effective way.
Download the free brochure
